huge lanes in the run game and he can
hold up against stronger rushers, too.
>> I don't know if you heard that, but
Chris Beam is in the back. He's telling
us that we have the newest Dallas Cowboy
on the line. Caleb DS is on the phone.
Caleb, first off, congratulations to you
and your family for a lifechanging day.
Just tell us what's going through your
mind right now as you were picked 11th
overall for the Cowboys.
>> Yeah, just extremely exciting, extremely
blessed to be here. uh very highly
favored and um just
just excited to be uh be a cowboy ready
to go play football.
>> What was it like through the draft
process getting to know the the Cowboys
front office? We heard your secret audio
with with the coaching staff and talking
to Brian Shottenheimimer about shooting
hoops and playing putt putt. I mean,
what was it like and how much contact
did Dallas have with you uh over the
last few months?
>> Yeah, I knew there was a a big interest
there and I was I was really excited
about that interest. Uh I had a great
feeling on our 30 visit and uh had a
great great visit formal visit with them
as well. So actually we didn't have a
formal visit. We actually missed out on
that. So uh but it all worked out in the
end. So uh yeah I mean great great to be
around coach Shotti. Um I appreciate the
Joneses for making this uh
making this pick and I'm just very
thankful to be in the situation I am.
>> Hey Caleb, congratulations. You
mentioned that 30 visit while you were
going around and and meeting this
Cowboys coaching staff and Christian
Parker, the defensive coordinator, what
were some of the things they were
telling you about if you did end up here
like you are now where they feel like
they can use you in the secondary to
help this defense?
>> Yeah, just being able to play in uh a
lot of different facets, be able to make
plays near the line of scrimmage and in
the deep part of the field. So, uh was
very interested in how they were going
to use me and um so we'll see how it
goes now and I'm excited.
>> Caleb, welcome to Dallas. you know,
there's a a a obviously a an air error
that comes with being a Cowboy and and
and a level of weight that comes with
that. Uh why do you think you're
prepared for everything that comes with
being a Dallas Cowboy?
>> Uh I think I'm just prepared in myself,
honestly. Um I played on big stages
before and I'll continue to be me no
matter where I go and I'm just uh I just
say, yeah, that's just myself. That's
who I am.
>> Caleb, I I want you to talk to fans
about what they are getting, not only on
the field, but off the field. But I want
you to talk about your temperament,
everything that uh is Caleb DS that's
going to be arriving in Dallas in the
next 24 hours.
>> Yeah, you're getting a man of faith. Uh
somebody that leaves leaves with their
faith first. Um and everything else,
he's just humble and hungry. Uh ready to
go get it. Uh ready to put in the
effort, ready to put in the time to go
out and do it. And uh just just trying
to make an impact, make plays on the
field.
>> And then last year's first round pick
was Tyler Booker. You spent a year with
him at Alabama. Y'all good friends?
>> Great people. Yeah, he was just in the
green room. I gave him a big hug when
they when I walked by him. Uh we lowkey
talked about it a little earlier today.
So, uh I'm just excited. Blessed.
>> Caleb, we heard that you beat coach in a
putting contest. What's our handicapping
golf? What do we got going there? We got
we got sticks.
>> I'm like a 14 and a half handicap. So,
I'm like 86 87 right around there. But
yeah, he had he struggled that day.
>> He struggled. Well, I'll tell you what,
they they've got they've got plenty of
great golf course. I know that golf
course at Ohio State is legendary, but
we got we got some good golf courses
here. So, we're looking forward to
having you out there, man.
>> Well, I'm I'll be out there soon, so you
can count on that.
>> No doubt about it. Caleb, uh, once
again, congratulations on being the
newest Dallas Cowboy. Can't wait to talk
to you a little bit more down the line
and and we'll see you at the Star
tomorrow.
>> All right. Appreciate y'all. Thank you.
>> There he goes. Caleb Down, safety from
Ohio State. Cowboys 11th overall pick
here in the 2026 NFL draft. You're
listening to our 2026 NFL draft coverage
on the Dallas Cowboys Radio Network and
DallasCowboys.com.